[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "You know why I think they're so excited to see you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "why", "I", "think", "they", "'re", "so", "excited", "to", "see", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Was it Daniel Craig or Denzel Washington who got Oscar nominated?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "Daniel", "Craig", "or", "Denzel", "Washington", "who", "got", "Oscar", "nominated", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "I don't know but I --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "but", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Daniel Craig"], "LOCATION": ["Denzel Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "That wasn't too big a build-up there, Doug?", "question_tokens": ["That", "was", "n't", "too", "big", "a", "build-up", "there", ",", "Doug", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "EX", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Doug"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "When you watched him tonight, did you feel like I did, you saw a man more at peace with himself perhaps now ready for the challenge of maybe being some real action in the second term?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "watched", "him", "tonight", ",", "did", "you", "feel", "like", "I", "did", ",", "you", "saw", "a", "man", "more", "at", "peace", "with", "himself", "perhaps", "now", "ready", "for", "the", "challenge", "of", "maybe", "being", "some", "real", "action", "in", "the", "second", "term", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "This is Barack Obama at his best.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "Barack", "Obama", "at", "his", "best", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "How significant is that going to be in his second term?", "question_tokens": ["How", "significant", "is", "that", "going", "to", "be", "in", "his", "second", "term", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Well, my hope is it's going to be very significant.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "hope", "is", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "very", "significant", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Does that bring with it a certain stability to the administration of the United States?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "bring", "with", "it", "a", "certain", "stability", "to", "the", "administration", "of", "the", "United", "States", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "I think it does.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dwight Eisenhower"]}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Is that going to be a significant help to him?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "going", "to", "be", "a", "significant", "help", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "You know, but think about second term Dwight Eisenhower.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "but", "think", "about", "second", "term", "Dwight", "Eisenhower", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "What should he be looking to do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "he", "be", "looking", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Well, there's all this stuff that's been on the table, you know, that's been talked about in the media, immigration reform.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "all", "this", "stuff", "that", "'s", "been", "on", "the", "table", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "'s", "been", "talked", "about", "in", "the", "media", ",", "immigration", "reform", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "DT", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "What would you love to see his legacy end up being after four more years?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "love", "to", "see", "his", "legacy", "end", "up", "being", "after", "four", "more", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Well, I think ultimately the legacy that he's after, the legacy that we're all working for is to revitalize this economy and the country in such a way that the -- there's new vitality that American compact that say s if you work hard you can get ahead.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "ultimately", "the", "legacy", "that", "he", "'s", "after", ",", "the", "legacy", "that", "we", "'re", "all", "working", "for", "is", "to", "revitalize", "this", "economy", "and", "the", "country", "in", "such", "a", "way", "that", "the", "--", "there", "'s", "new", "vitality", "that", "American", "compact", "that", "say", "s", "if", "you", "work", "hard", "you", "can", "get", "ahead", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "What would you say they would be for him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "they", "would", "be", "for", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Well, you know, I'm going to point to his own words.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "point", "to", "his", "own", "words", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "What else do you see as priorities?", "question_tokens": ["What", "else", "do", "you", "see", "as", "priorities", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Immigration reform.", "answer_tokens": ["Immigration", "reform", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Do you think the president has the political clout and the personal drive to try and pursue an assault weapons ban if it looks like he can't?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "president", "has", "the", "political", "clout", "and", "the", "personal", "drive", "to", "try", "and", "pursue", "an", "assault", "weapons", "ban", "if", "it", "looks", "like", "he", "ca", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Well, I think he's already made that clear.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "already", "made", "that", "clear", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Can he succeed?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "he", "succeed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Well, you know, let's see.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "let", "'s", "see", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "I'm splendid, thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "splendid", ",", "thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "And you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "I'm extremely honored to be talking to you, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "extremely", "honored", "to", "be", "talking", "to", "you", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "And how do you think he's done, President Obama, in his first term and what would you like him to do more of in his second term?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "done", ",", "President", "Obama", ",", "in", "his", "first", "term", "and", "what", "would", "you", "like", "him", "to", "do", "more", "of", "in", "his", "second", "term", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Well, I think he's done the best he could.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "done", "the", "best", "he", "could", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "What advice do you think he would have given the president for his second and final term of office?", "question_tokens": ["What", "advice", "do", "you", "think", "he", "would", "have", "given", "the", "president", "for", "his", "second", "and", "final", "term", "of", "office", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "Thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "What did you make of what she said and in particular about what Martin Luther King may have said to Barack Obama?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "what", "she", "said", "and", "in", "particular", "about", "what", "Martin", "Luther", "King", "may", "have", "said", "to", "Barack", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Well, just -- I thought it was very moving and you got a nice call-out there from her.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "just", "--", "I", "thought", "it", "was", "very", "moving", "and", "you", "got", "a", "nice", "call-out", "there", "from", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Martin Luther King"], "PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Nick Cannon, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Nick", "Cannon", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "I'm great, man.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "great", ",", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nick Cannon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "For you as a young black American, what does it mean to you, that day, the significance of both these great men being commemorated on this day?", "question_tokens": ["For", "you", "as", "a", "young", "black", "American", ",", "what", "does", "it", "mean", "to", "you", ",", "that", "day", ",", "the", "significance", "of", "both", "these", "great", "men", "being", "commemorated", "on", "this", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "I mean, it's outstanding.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "outstanding", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "CC", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "What should the president be doing, though, to get more people like you to get up there and live the dream again?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "the", "president", "be", "doing", ",", "though", ",", "to", "get", "more", "people", "like", "you", "to", "get", "up", "there", "and", "live", "the", "dream", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "DT", "NN", "VB", "VBG", ",", "IN", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "CC", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "I mean, the millennial generation really is a generation of young people who want to do better and all about empowerment.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "the", "millennial", "generation", "really", "is", "a", "generation", "of", "young", "people", "who", "want", "to", "do", "better", "and", "all", "about", "empowerment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "ANNON: What does that have to do with talent, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["ANNON", ":", "What", "does", "that", "have", "to", "do", "with", "talent", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "I think it's talent.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "talent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "Is she as attractive as last time I saw her?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "she", "as", "attractive", "as", "last", "time", "I", "saw", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "She's just as beautiful.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "just", "as", "beautiful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1840"], "PERSON": ["William Henry Harrison"]}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "CD", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "Tomorrow, talk me through what's actually going to happen?", "question_tokens": ["Tomorrow", ",", "talk", "me", "through", "what", "'s", "actually", "going", "to", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "Well, I've got to tell you, in 1840, William Henry Harrison got elected and the inaugural in '41 and did not wear a coat.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "got", "to", "tell", "you", ",", "in", "1840", ",", "William", "Henry", "Harrison", "got", "elected", "and", "the", "inaugural", "in", "'41", "and", "did", "not", "wear", "a", "coat", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Nobel Peace Prize"], "PERSON": ["Dr. King"]}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "How can he force through his agenda in a smart way?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "he", "force", "through", "his", "agenda", "in", "a", "smart", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "Well, remember, like Dr. King, he's won a Nobel Peace Prize, he's an international figure and the world is going to be watching tomorrow.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "remember", ",", "like", "Dr.", "King", ",", "he", "'s", "won", "a", "Nobel", "Peace", "Prize", ",", "he", "'s", "an", "international", "figure", "and", "the", "world", "is", "going", "to", "be", "watching", "tomorrow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "We get the feeling that the Americans perhaps slight realized that continuing to be at war with the president isn't necessarily in the national interest?", "question_tokens": ["We", "get", "the", "feeling", "that", "the", "Americans", "perhaps", "slight", "realized", "that", "continuing", "to", "be", "at", "war", "with", "the", "president", "is", "n't", "necessarily", "in", "the", "national", "interest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "Yet to be seen because of the way the money, I think.", "answer_tokens": ["Yet", "to", "be", "seen", "because", "of", "the", "way", "the", "money", ",", "I", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]